A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991, RG 39 FA1505
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1987-1991; 39
  - International Relations, 1987-1991; 15
    - International Foundation for the Survival and Development of Humanity - Cousins (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - International Human Development Project (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - International Institute for Strategic Studies (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - International Rescue Committee, Inc. (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Internews Network (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Internews Network - Cousins (Box 296, Folder 3-4)
    - North American Institute (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) - Cousins (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Roosevelt Center for American Policy Studies (Box 297, Folder 2-3, Box 298, Folder 1)
    - Spanish Institute (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - World Affairs Council of Inland Southern California (Box 298, Folder 2)
    - World Centre (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - World Service (Box 298, Folder 3)
    - Afghanistan - A-Z (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Africa - A-Z (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Africa - A-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 298, Folder 4-5)
    - Africa - African American Institute (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - Africa - African American Institute - Cousins (Box 298, Folder 6)
    - Asia - A-Z (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - Asia - A-Z - Cousins (Box 298, Folder 7)
    - Asia - Asia Society (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Asia - Asia Society - A-Z (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Asia - Asia Society - Contributions (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Asia - Asian Cultural Council (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - Asia - East-West Center Foundation (Box 300, Folder 5, Box 301, Folder 1-4)
    - Asia - East-West Center Foundation - Annual Reports (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - Asia - East-West Center Foundation - Fundraising (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - Asia - East-West Center Foundation - Meetings, 1987-1990 (Box 302, Folder 3-4)
    - Asia - East-West Center Foundation - Printed Material (Box 302, Folder 5, Box 303, Folder 1-3, Box 304, Folder 1-2)
    - Australia - A-Z (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - Austria - A-Z (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Brazil (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - Burma - A-Z (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - Canada - A-Z (Box 304, Folder 7)
    - Chile - A-Z (Box 304, Folder 8)
    - China (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - China - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - China - America China Society (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - China - National Committe on United States China Relations (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - Costa Rica - A-Z (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - Cuba - A-Z (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - Ecuador (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - El Salvador (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - El Salvador - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 2)
    - Ethiopia - A-Z (Box 305, Folder 8)
    - France - A-Z (Box 305, Folder 9)
    - France - American Committee on the French Revolution (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - France - French-American Foundation (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - France - Institut Charles de Gaulle (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - Germany (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - Greece - A-Z (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - Guinea - A-Z (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - India - A-Z (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - Iran (Box 306, Folder 8)
    - Ireland (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - Israel - A-Z (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - Israel - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 3)
    - Israel - Jerusalem Foundation (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - Italy - A-Z (Box 307, Folder 4)
    - Italy - Philip Mazzei Association (Box 307, Folder 5)
    - Japan - A-I (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - Japan - J-Z (Box 308, Folder 1-2)
    - Japan - Japan Center for International Exchange (Box 308, Folder 3-4)
    - Japan - Japan Society (Box 308, Folder 5)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - Japan - Japan Society - Contributions - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 4)
    - Japan - Japan Foundation (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - Kenya (Box 309, Folder 3)
    - Mexico - A-Z (Box 309, Folder 4)
    - Mexico - A-Z - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Middle East (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - Middle East - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - Pakistan - A-Z (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - Peru - A-Z (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - Philippines - A-Z (Box 310, Folder 4)
    - Poland - A-Z (Box 310, Folder 5)
    - Portugal - A-Z (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - Romania (Box 310, Folder 7)
    - South Africa - A-Z (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - South Africa - A-Z - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - Spain - A-Z (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Thailand (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Thailand - Thai-American Friendship Committee (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - USSR - A-I (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - USSR - I-Z (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - USSR - A-Z - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - USSR - Center for U.S.-U.S.S.R. Initiatives (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - USSR - Commission on U.S.-Soviet Relations (Box 313, Folder 10)
    - USSR - The Entertainment Summit (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - USSR - Entertainment Summit - Cousins (Box 313, Folder 11)
    - USSR - Informal US-Soviet Conference (Dartmouth Conference) (Box 312, Folder 2-4)
    - Foreign Aid - A-Z (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Aid - A-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 313, Folder 12-13)
    - Foreign Aid - Care (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Aid - Citizens Network for Foreign Affairs, 1987-1991 (Box 314, Folder 3-4)
    - Foreign Aid - Citizens Network for Economic and Security Assistance, 1986 (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Aid - Hunger Project (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Aid - Hunger Project - Cousins (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Aid - International Center for Development Policy (Box 315, Folder 2-3)
    - Foreign Aid - Neighbor to Neighbor (Action Fund) (Box 315, Folder 4, Box 317, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Aid - Overseas Development Council (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Aid - Overseas Development Council - Cousins (Box 317, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Aid - Resources Development Foundation (Box 316, Folder 2-3)
    - Foreign Aid - Synergos Institute (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Aid - Synergos Institute - Cousins (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Policy - A-Z (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Policy - A-Z - Cousins (Box 317, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Policy - Committee for National Security - Cousins (Box 317, Folder 5, Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Contributions (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Contributions - Cousins (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Fundraising (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Middle East Trip, 1990 February (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - Southern Africa Study Group (Box 319, Folder 1-3)
    - Foreign Policy - Council on Foreign Relations - USSR Trip (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - Foreign Policy - Foreign Policy Association (Box 320, Folder 1-2)
    - Foreign Policy - National Committee on American Foreign Policy (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - A-C (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Pan American - D-Z (Box 321, Folder 1-2)
    - Pan American - A-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 328, Folder 3-7)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - A-L (Box 321, Folder 3-4)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - M-Z (Box 322, Folder 1-2)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - General Correspondence, 1990 (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Canadian Affairs, 1988-1991 (Box 322, Folder 4-5)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Canadian Affairs Program, 1987 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Chairman's International Advisory Council - A-Z (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Contributions (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Fundraising (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Fundraising, 1990 January 1 (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Fundraising Spring Party, 1991 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Fundraising Spring Party, 1989 June 6 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Fundraising Spring Party, 1988 June 9 (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Growth Study, 1985-1986 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Growth Study Distribution, 1986-1987 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Meetings (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Membership, 1984-1987 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Trips - Canada, 1990 May 31-June 1 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Trips - Ecuador, 1987 February (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Caribbean Central American Action - A-Z (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Caribbean Central American Action - Meetings (Box 326, Folder 4-5)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Center for Inter-American Affairs - A-Z (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Council of the Americas (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Consortium for Inter-American Trade and Development (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Pan American - Americas Society - Pan American Society - A-Z (Box 327, Folder 4)
    - Peace - C (Box 327, Folder 5)
    - Peace - D-S (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - Peace - T-Z (Box 329, Folder 1-2)
    - Peace - A-B - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 328, Folder 8)
    - Peace - C - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 317, Folder 6-7)
    - Peace - D-S - Cousins (Box 331, Folder 1-4)
    - Peace - T-W - Cousins (Box 332, Folder 1-3)
    - Peace - Access a Security Information Service (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Architects-Designers-Planners for Social Responsibility (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Better World Society (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Peace - Better World Society - Cousins (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Bilderberg Meetings (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Business Executives for National Security Education Fund, Inc. (Box 329, Folder 5)
    - Peace - Business Executives for National Security Education Fund, Inc. - Printer Matter (Box 330, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Business Executives for National Security Education Fund, Inc. - Cousins (Box 333, Folder 3, Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Campaign for Peace and Democracy/East and West (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Center for Economic Conversion (Box 334, Folder 3)
    - Peace - Center for Education on Nuclear War, Inc. (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Center for Innovative Diplomacy (Box 335, Folder 1-2, Box 336, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Center for Psychological Studies in the Nuclear Age (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Citizen Alert (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Citizen Exchange Council (Box 330, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Citizen Exchange Council - Cousins (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Communications Consortium (Box 334, Folder 5, Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Council for a Livable World Education Fund (Box 335, Folder 3, Box 338, Folder 2-3)
    - Peace - Downwinders (Box 339, Folder 1-2)
    - Peace- Educators for Social Responsibility (Box 339, Folder 3, Box 340, Folder 1)
    - Peace - The Forum Foundation (The Forum Institute) (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Foundation for the Arts of Peace (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Peace - Foundation for International Security (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Global Outlook Education Institute (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - Peace - Dana McLean Greeley Foundation for Peace and Justice, Inc. (Box 341, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Institute for Peace and International Security (Box 341, Folder 2-3)
    - Peace - Interamerican Research Center (Box 341, Folder 4)
    - Peace - International Peace Academy (Box 330, Folder 3)
    - Peace - International Peace Academy - Cousins (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - Peace - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, Inc. (Box 330, Folder 4)
    - Peace - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, Inc. - Cousins (Box 342, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Jobs With Peace, Inc. and Jobs with Peace Education Fund, Inc. (Box 342, Folder 2-3)
    - Peace - Lawyers Alliance for Nuclear Arms Control, Inc. (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - Peace - National Campaign to Save the ABM Treaty (Box 343, Folder 2-3)
    - Peace - National Commission for Economic Conversion and Disarmament (Box 343, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Nuclear Times, Inc. (Box 343, Folder 5)
    - Peace - Nuclear Control Institute (Box 344, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Options (Box 344, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Parliamentarians Global Action (Box 344, Folder 3)
    - Peace - Peace Child Foundation (Box 345, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Peace and Common Security (Box 345, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Peace Development Fund (Box 345, Folder 3, Box 347, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Peace Links (Box 347, Folder 3)
    - Peace - The Peace Through Law Education Fund (Box 346, Folder 1)
    - Peace - The Peace Through Law Education Fund - Cousins (Box 347, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Ploughshares Fund (Box 346, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Ploughshares Fund - Cousins (Box 348, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Richard Pollock Associates (Box 347, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Sadat Peace Foundation (Box 346, Folder 5)
    - Peace - Sadat Peace Foundation - Cousins (Box 348, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Safer World, Inc. (Box 348, Folder 3)
    - Peace - Sane (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Sane Education Fund of Pennsylvania (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Sane-Freeze Education Fund (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - Peace - Search for Common Ground (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Peace - Search for Common Ground - Cousins (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Up With People (Box 346, Folder 4)
    - Peace - Washington Council on Non-Proliferation (Box 350, Folder 1)
    - Peace - Wisconsin Project on Nuclear Arms Control (Box 350, Folder 2)
    - Peace - Women for a Meaningful Summit (Box 350, Folder 3)
    - Peace - Women's Action for Nuclear Disarmament Education Fund, Inc. (Box 350, Folder 4)
    - Peace - World Policy Institute (Box 351, Folder 1-2)
    - United Nations (Box 346, Folder 6)
    - United Nations - A-M (Box 346, Folder 7)
    - United Nations - N-Z (Box 352, Folder 1)
    - United Nations - N-Z - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 1)
    - United Nations - Business Council for the United Nations (Box 352, Folder 2)
    - United Nations - Friends of the United Nations (Box 351, Folder 3)
    - United Nations - United Nations Association of the United States of America (Box 352, Folder 3)
    - United Nations - International Children's Emergency Fund (UNICEF) (Box 352, Folder 4)
    - United Nations - United Nations International Children's Fund (UNICEF) - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 2)
    - United Nations - United Nations Development Fund for Women (UNIFEM) (Box 352, Folder 5)
    - United Nations - United Nations Development Program (UNDP) (Box 352, Folder 6)
    - United Nations - United Nations Environment Programme (Box 352, Folder 7)
    - United Nations - University of Peace (Box 353, Folder 1)
    - United States Government - Agency for International Development - International Executive Service Corps (Box 353, Folder 2)
    - United States Government - Executive Council on Foreign Diplomats (Box 353, Folder 3)
    - United States Government - Department of State - A-Z (Box 353, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Department of State - Fine Arts Committee (Box 353, Folder 5)
    - United States Government - Department of State - Friends of Art and Preservation in Embassies (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - J-M, 1987-1991; 16
    - J - Miscellaneous (Box 354, Folder 2)
    - K - Miscellaneous (Box 354, Folder 3)
    - K - Miscellaneous - Katzenback, L. Emery & Mrs. Shirley Steinman (Box 354, Folder 4)
    - L - Miscellaneous (Box 354, Folder 5)
    - M - Miscellaneous (Box 354, Folder 6)
  - Medicine, 1987-1991; 17
    - Medicine - A (Box 354, Folder 7)
    - Medicine - B-G (Box 355, Folder 1-4)
    - Medicine - H-O (Box 356, Folder 1-4)
    - Medicine - P-Z (Box 357, Folder 1-3)
    - Medicine - A-Z - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 3-13)
    - Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Association (Box 359, Folder 1)
    - Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Association - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 14)
    - American Association of Ayurvedic Medicine (Box 359, Folder 2-3)
    - American Cancer Society (Box 360, Folder 1-2)
    - American Cancer Society - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 15)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research (Box 360, Folder 3)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 358, Folder 16-17)
    - American Heath Foundation (Box 360, Folder 4)
    - Amigos de las Americas (Box 361, Folder 1)
    - Arthritis Foundation, Inc. (Box 361, Folder 2)
    - Botanical Dimensions (Box 361, Folder 3)
    - Cancer Care, Inc. (Box 361, Folder 4)
    - Cancer Research Institute (Box 361, Folder 5)
    - Cancer Research Institute, Inc. - Cousins (Box 358, Folder 18)
    - Deafness Research Foundation (Box 361, Folder 6)
    - Doctors Without Borders USA, Inc. (Box 362, Folder 1)
    - Fetzer Institute (Box 362, Folder 2)
    - General Motors Cancer Research Foundation (Box 362, Folder 3)
    - House Ear Institute (Box 362, Folder 4)
    - Institute for the Advancement of Health (Box 362, Folder 5, Box 363, Folder 1-2)
    - Institute for the Advancement of Health - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 1)
    - Institute for Holistic Blood Diagnosis (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Humanistic Science (Box 363, Folder 4)
    - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation (Box 364, Folder 1-2)
    - Harvard Medical School (Box 364, Folder 3)
    - Lancaster Foundation (Box 364, Folder 4)
    - Maharishi-Ayurveda Association of America and Health Center (Box 364, Folder 5, Box 365, Folder 1)
    - The Robert Mapplethorpe Laboratory for Aids Research (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - Medical Illness Counseling Center (Box 365, Folder 3)
    - Medical Illness Counseling Center - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 2)
    - Mind-Body Medical Institute (Box 365, Folder 4)
    - Mind-Body Medical Institute - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 3)
    - National Council on Alcoholism and Drug Dependence (Box 366, Folder 1-2)
    - National Foundation for Cancer Research (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - National Foundation for Facial Reconstruction (Box 366, Folder 4)
    - National Organization for Circumcision Information Resource Centers (Box 366, Folder 5)
    - National Multiple Sclerosis Society (Box 366, Folder 6)
    - New York Academy of Medicine (Box 366, Folder 7)
    - New York Blood Center (Box 367, Folder 1)
    - Open Door Family Health Centers (Box 367, Folder 2)
    - Oubre, Alondra Yvette (Box 367, Folder 3)
    - Physicians for Social Responsibility (Box 367, Folder 4)
    - Physicians for Social Responsibility - Cousins (Box 373, Folder 4)
    - The Skin Cancer Foundation (Box 367, Folder 5)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Association, Inc. (Box 367, Folder 6)
    - Ann Wigmore Foundation (Box 368, Folder 1-2)
    - Alcoholism - A-Z (Box 367, Folder 3)
    - Alcoholism - Alcoholism Council of Greater New York (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - Alcoholism - Children of Acoholics Foundation, Inc. (Box 369, Folder 2-3)
    - Alcoholism - Freedom Institute (Box 369, Folder 4)
    - Alcoholism - National Council of Alcoholism (Box 369, Folder 5, Box 370, Folder 1)
    - Alcoholism - National Council of Alcoholism - Fundraising (Box 370, Folder 2)
    - Alcoholism - The Weekend Center (Box 370, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - A-D (Box 370, Folder 4-5)
    - Hospitals - E-Z (Box 371, Folder 1-4)
    - Hospitals - A-Z - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 373, Folder 5-11)
    - Hospitals - Charing Cross Westminster Medical College (Box 371, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Columbia-Presbyterian Medical Center, NY, NY (Box 372, Folder 1-2)
    - Hospitals - Dartmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center (Box 372, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Eisenhower Medical Center (Box 372, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Harlem Hospital Center (Box 374, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Hospital for Special Surgery (Box 374, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - A-M (Box 374, Folder 3-4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - N-Z (Box 375, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Annual Reports (Box 375, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Board of Overseers, Board of Managers (Box 375, Folder 3, Box 376, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Center for Diagnostic Imaging and Breast Cancer (Box 376, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions (Box 376, Folder 3-4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions - Cousins and Fifth Generation (Box 373, Folder 12-13)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Contributions JY Ranch, 1978-1991 (Box 376, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Convocation (Box 376, Folder 6)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Audit Committee (Box 377, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Finances - Joint Finance and Funding Committee, 1987 (Box 377, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - General (Box 377, Folder 4, Box 378, Folder 1-2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - A-M (Box 378, Folder 3-5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - N-Z (Box 379, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Japan (Box 379, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Kluge, John (Box 379, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Fundraising - Sinatra VII (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Galbraith, Mrs. Evan G. Jr. (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Enid A. Haupt Pavilion (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Joint Nominating Committee (Box 380, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings (Box 380, Folder 5)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Managers 1991 (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Managers 1989, 1989 September 27; May 24 1989 (Box 381, Folder 1-2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Managers 1989, 1989 January 25 (Box 381, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Managers 1988, 1988 January 27 (Box 381, Folder 4)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Managers 1988, 1988 May 25 (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Overseers 1989, 1989 July 26 (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Overseers, Board of Managers 1987, 1987 March 25 (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - Hospitals - Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Meetings - Board of Overseers, Board of Managers 1987, 1987 July 22 (Box 382, Folder 4)